<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SpaceTime</string>
    <string name="description">The application allows you to determine the magnitude of the effect of gravitational time
        dilation in the field of massive objects. Do you want to know?
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">InfoActivity</string>
    <string name="title_info">Mobile application “SpaceTime”</string>
    <string name="large_text">
       "is a smart service that allows you to determine the magnitude of the effect of gravitational time dilation in the field of massive objects. Using the application, you will be able to visually experience the physical concept of relativity over the time of general relativity."
    </string>
    <string name="text_time">
        Time is undoubtedly your most valuable resource. You want to know how to extend it, but the search for the elixir of eternal life is unsuccessful, and the time machine does not work yet. And you knew that modern physics claims that the flow of time is relative and depends on the speed of an object (the so-called relativistic deceleration) and its position in space relative to massive bodies (gravitational deceleration), such as planets, stars, and even black holes. The stronger the gravity, the slower time flows. The fact is that the fabric of space and time are the same, and therefore the flow of time, like space, is bent under the action of the gravitational field.
    </string>
    <string name="text_app">With this application, you can get the most accurate information about how much your own time flows faster if you climbed a high mountain or fly a plane than on the surface of the Earth.</string>
    <string name="text_timetime">Of course, this difference is negligible. The difference between the time measured by the clock on the tops of the mountains and on the surface of the Earth is just a few nanoseconds. And yes, given this phenomenon, it turns out that your legs - albeit infinitely slightly - are younger than your head.</string>
    <string name="txt_nickname">Your nickname</string>
    <string name="txt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="text_app_1">"If you want to understand better - the work of Einstein on the General Theory of Relativity is already waiting for you!\n" "It was about this effect that the heroine Anne Hathaway spoke to the character Matthew McConaughey in Interstellar after descending to a distant Miller planet orbiting the black hole Gargantua: “One hour on this planet is equal to seven Earth years”."</string>
    <string name="start">Let\'s Discover This</string>
    <string name="start_anon">Or stay anonymous and continue</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to SpaceTime</string>
    <string name="txt_changes">Current Changes</string>
    <string name="txt_date">01 Jun, 2019</string>
    <string name="txt_date_date">your values</string>
    <string name="txt_up">You can also calculate your own parameters to search for changes</string>
    <string name="txt_up_btn">Try It!</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_miller">Do you want to know how long your life can be extended if your new home becomes the planet Miller near the black hole Gargantua?</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_time">time dilation</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_distance">distance from the hole to the planet</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_mass">hole mass</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_value">value</string>
    <string name="text_app_faq">"The application is an addition to our research project on mathematical modeling“ \n The Earth Near Gargantua " \n" "To familiarize yourself with our scientific work, you can follow the links"</string>
</resources>
